Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
6046
Kheel Center
388.2 linear ft.
Pamphlets, publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
The Archives Union File is a collection of publications of United States labor unions. Included is information on the American Institute for Free Labor Development. The AUF collection consists largely of pamphlets and publications of unions, collected by the Kheel Center.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into twelve sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
AFL-CIO --Archives; AFL-CIO. American Institute for Free Labor Development--Archives; AFL-CIO. Building and Construction Trades Dept.--Archives; AFL-CIO. Department of Economic Research--Archives; AFL-CIO. Education Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Executive Council--Archives; AFL-CIO. Human Resources Development Institute--Archives; AFL-CIO. Industrial Union Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Legislative Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Public Employees Department--Archives; AFSCME --Archives; Air Line Pilots Association --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Research Department--Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; American Association of University Professors --Archives; American Federation of Government Employees --Archives; American Federation of Labor --Archives; American Federation of Musicians --Archives; American Federation of Teachers --Archives; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists --Archives; American Guild of Musical Artists --Archives; American Postal Workers Union --Archives; Association of Flight Attendants (U.S.) --Archives; Bakery, Confectionary and Tobacco Workers International Union --Archives; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.) --Archives; Communication Workers Union --Archives; Communications Workers of America --Archives; Congress of Industrial Organizations --Archives; Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions --Archives; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union --Archives; Illinois State AFL-CIO --Archives; Industrial Workers of the World --Archives; International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers --Archives; International Association of Fire Fighters --Archives; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers --Archives; International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades --Archives; International Brotherhood of Teamsters --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union. Educational Department--Archives; International Longshoremens and Warehousemens Union --Archives; International Typographical Union --Archives; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; International Union of North American Laborers --Archives; International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Ford Dept. --Archives; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers --Archives; Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.) --Archives; National Association of Postal Supervisors --Archives; National Maritime Union of America --Archives; National Writers Union (U.S.) --Archives; New York State AFL-CIO --Archives; New York State United Teachers --Archives; Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union --Archives; Screen Actors Guild --Archives; Service Employees International Union --Archives; Sheet Metal Workers International Union --Archives; Teamsters for a Democratic Union --Archives; Textile Workers Union of America --Archives; United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry --Archives; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America --Archives; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; United Glass & Ceramic Workers of North America --Archives; United Mine Workers of America --Archives; United Office and Professionals Workers of America --Archives; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America --Archives; United Steelworkers of America --Archives; Utility Workers Union of America --Archives; Writer's Guild of America --Archives
Subjects:
Agricultural laborers--Labor unions; Airlines--Employees--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Barbers--Labor unions; Building-service employees--Labor unions; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Construction workers--Labor unions; Automobile industry workers--Labor unions; Bakery employees--Labor unions; Transport workers--Labor unions; Fire fighters--Labor unions; Electricians--Labor unions; Plumbers--Labor unions; Teachers--Labor unions; Glassworkers--Labor unions; Restaurants--Employees--Labor unions; Postal service--Employees--Labor unions; Rubber industry and trade--Labor unions
Form and Genre Terms:
Pamphlets.; Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this collection:
6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this point.
Related Collections:
6046 mf: Archives Union File on Microfilm
CONTAINER LIST
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union) (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Cutters' almanac, 1902-1962, Publication (Box 192, Folder 1)
    Author: Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union.
    Notes: 2 copies
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: Fiftieth Anniv. Celebration, 1902-1952, Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10, ILGWU, Publication (Box 192, Folder 1)
    Notes: Program. 2 copies
  - Item 3: Handbook for members, Publication (Box 192, Folder 1)
    Author: Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New Union Health Plan, 1945; Publication (Box 192, Folder 2)
    Notes: Reprinted from Industrial Medicine, Feb. 1945
  - Item 2: The left wing in the garment unions, 1927; Publication (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Why this strike?, 1935; Publication (Box 192, Folder 2)
    Author: Julius Hochman.
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Bulletin of the Joint Board of Sanitary control in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt and the Dress and Waist Industries., 1914; Publication (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Directory of certificated shops in the cloak, suit and skirt industry, 1913; Publication (Box 192, Folder 3)
    Author: Joint Board of Sanitary Control in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt and the Dress and Waist Industries, New York.
  - Item 3: Light and illumination in garment shops, 1918; Publication (Box 192, Folder 3)
    Author: Price, George Moses
  - Item 4: Seating and Posture, 1923; Publication (Box 192, Folder 3)
    Notes: Booklet of articles about the seating conditions in the Women's Garment Trades
  - Item 5: Six years' work and progress of the Joint Board of Sanitary Control in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt and the Dress and Waist Industries, 1917; Publication (Box 192, Folder 3)
    Author: Joint Board of Sanitary Control in the Cloak, Suit and Skirt and the Dress and Waist Industries, New York
  - Item 6: Special report on sanitary conditions in the shops of the dress and waist industry; a preliminary report, 1913; Publication (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The Joint Board of Sanitary Controlsummary of data gathered by the fourteenth annual re-inspection of the shops, 1924; Publication (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: The Prosanis Label of the Joint Board of Sanitary Control, Publication (Box 192, Folder 3)
    Author: Henry Moskowitz
  - Item 9: The Union Dental Clinic, 1918; Publication (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Union benefits, medical and other benefits in labor organizations, 1918; Publication (Box 192, Folder 3)
    Author: George M. Price
  - Item 11: Union dental clinic for the workers in the ILGWU, 1917; Publication (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Workers' Health Bulletin, 1915; Publication (Box 192, Folder 3)
    Notes: Fifth year no. 3 (1915)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Cartoons, 1947-1950, from "Justice", Publication (Box 192, Folder 4)
    Author: Bernard Seaman
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Knitgoods Workers Voice, 1956; Publication (Box 192, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 19, no.1-5 (1956)
  - Item 2: Knitgoods Workers Voice, 1957; Publication (Box 192, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 20, no. 1-4 (1957)
  - Item 3: Knitgoods Workers Voice, 1958; Publication (Box 192, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 21, no.1-5 (1958)
  - Item 4: Knitgoods Workers Voice, 1959; Publication (Box 192, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 22, no.1-4 (1959)
  - Item 5: Knitgoods Workers Voice, 1964; Publication (Box 192, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 28, no.3,5 (1964)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The ILGWU legal department, 1957; Publication (Box 192, Folder 6)
    Author: Morris P. Glushien
    Notes: Copy 2
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The labor movement and the NRA: the standpoint of progressive unionism., 1934; Publication (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: American labor and racial equality, Publication (Box 192, Folder 7)
    Author: Charles S. Zimmerman
  - Item 3: American labor faces the future, 1934; Publication (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Bulletin, 1922; Publication (Box 192, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan. 1922. Issued monthly by the United Shop Delegates' League of the Ladies Garment Industry
  - Item 5: Educational Dept., Dressmakers Union Local 22, ILGWU, Publication (Box 192, Folder 7)
    Notes: Advertisement. 2 copies
  - Item 6: Know your price settlements: it can mean more money in your pay envelope, Publication (Box 192, Folder 7)
    Notes: Employee handbook
  - Item 7: Local 10 forges ahead, 1941; Publication (Box 192, Folder 7)
    Author: Isidore Nagler
  - Item 8: Mooney and Billings must be freed!, 1936; Publication (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Our Union at work, Summary report of the executive board of Dressmakers Union, Local 22, I.L.G.W.U., for the year April 1933 to April 1934, Publication (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Report of the Dressmakers Union of Greater New York, Local 22, 1922; Publication (Box 192, Folder 7)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 22 (New York, N.Y.)
  - Item 11: Report on the medical administration of sick benefits to Dressmakers' Union Local 22 of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union for the year 1935, 1936; Publication (Box 192, Folder 7)
    Author: Leo Price
  - Item 12: The C.I.O. at the convention of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Atlantic City, May, 1937, Publication (Box 192, Folder 7)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: A Look back: pages out of American labor's past., 1950; Publication (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: An outline of the problems involved in this strike guide to speakers prepared by the speakers' committee., 1930; Publication (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Labor stuff - project for a Local 22 Union School Magazine, 1939; Publication (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Labor stuff by members of the Labor Journalism Class, Dressmakers Union, Local 22, ILGWU, 1938; Publication (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: We're glad you're here, Publication (Box 192, Folder 8)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Central School 1936-1937 - Course - Critical periods in American trade unionism (Box 192, Folder 9)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Educational Dept.
    Notes: Class work
  - Item 2: Labor stuff by members of the Labor Journalism Class, Dressmakers Union, Local 22, ILGWU, 1938; Publication (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Report of the delegation of Local 22 on the 22nd Biennial Convention of the I.L.G.W.U., 1934; Publication (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Report of the Waterproof Garment Workers Union, Local 20, I.L.G.W.U., 1922; Publication (Box 192, Folder 9)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 20, Waterproof Garment Workers' Union.
  - Item 5: Resolutions of Dressmakers Union, Local 22 for the 22nd Biennial Convention of the I.L.G.W.U., 1934; Publication (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Review of the strike, Publication (Box 192, Folder 9)
    Author: Citizens' Emergency Committee
  - Item 7: Souvenir Journal..50th Anniv. (Manhattan Opera House), 1936; Publication (Box 192, Folder 9)
    Author: Cloak & Suit Operators Union. Local 1. ILGWU
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 192, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Souvenir Journal..50th Anniv. (Manhattan Opera House), 1936; Publication (Box 192, Folder 10)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A fighting program for the dressmakers, 1937; Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: A Look back: pages out of American labor's past., 1950; Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Labor Information bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1941 May
  - Item 4: Local 22 art workshop exhibition., 1944; Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Progressive Dressmaker, 1935; Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1 (1935)
  - Item 6: The C.I.O. at the convention of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Atlantic City, May, 1937, Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: The labor movement and the NRA: the standpoint of progressive unionism., 1934; Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The Union Dressmaker, 1934; Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1,3 (1934)
  - Item 9: What Unionism means to you!, Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Who are the lefts, Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: 22, 1948; Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1 (1948:Jan. 1)
  - Item 12: Bienvenido a nuestra union, Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Many craftsOne union!, Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: On complaints and grievances, Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Welcome to our union, Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Why the New Industrial Program?, Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: 7 Million Allies, Publication (Box 193, Folder 1)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Hourly table of wages from $9 to $50, Publication (Box 193, Folder 2)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 23- 25 (New York, N.Y.)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: and this is Local 32 ILGWU your union!..., 1953; Publication (Box 193, Folder 3)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 32
    Notes: Local booklet.
    Language: English;Spanish.
  - Item 2: Second Anniv. - Corset & Brassiere Workers' Union, Local 32, ILGWU, 1936; Publication (Box 193, Folder 3)
    Notes: Program
  - Item 3: Twentieth Anniv. - Local 32, ILGWU., 1954; Publication (Box 193, Folder 3)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A Cloakmaker Looks at Stolberg's "Tailors' Progress", 1944; Publication (Box 193, Folder 4)
    Author: Joseph Breslaw
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Beltmaker, 1960; Publication (Box 193, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 57, no. 4,6, 8, 12
  - Item 2: Beltmaker, 1961; Publication (Box 193, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 58, no. 5-6
  - Item 3: Beltmaker, 1962; Publication (Box 193, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 59, no.5
  - Item 4: Beltmaker, 1963; Publication (Box 193, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 60, no.1-2
  - Item 5: Beltmaker, 1964; Publication (Box 193, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 61, no. 1-2
  - Item 6: Beltmaker, 1949; Publication (Box 193, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 10, no.7-8, 10, 12
  - Item 7: Beltmaker, 1950; Publication (Box 193, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 11, no. 3,5
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Introducing Local 40, ILGWU, Publication (Box 193, Folder 6)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 40
  - Item 2: LA Union Health Center, ILGWU, 1951; Publication (Box 193, Folder 6)
    Notes: 1951 February 12
  - Item 3: Presentamos la Local 40, ILGWU, Publication (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: The Beltmakers: a history of Local 40, ILGWU, Publication (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Your Union and your union dues, Publication (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Your Union Health Center - "A Fortress Against Disease"ILGWU, Publication (Box 193, Folder 6)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Problems and prospects of the city's Dress Industry, 1954; Publication (Box 193, Folder 7)
    Author: Jack Sptizer
  - Item 2: Report of the Dress and Waist Pressers Union, Local 60: to the 22nd Convention of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1934; Publication (Box 193, Folder 7)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 60
  - Item 3: The Pressers: Pioneers forging ahead, Local 60, ILGWU, 1957; Publication (Box 193, Folder 7)
    Notes: Advertising booklet
  - Item 4: The Shipping Clerk, 1954; Publication (Box 193, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol.2:no.3 (1954)
  - Item 5: The Union Shipping Clerk: a handy reference guide to your rights, benefits, and responsibilities [Local 60], 1962; Publication (Box 193, Folder 7)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: A member of the I.L.G.W.U. family! The birth of Local 60-A and its achievements-1954-1956, Publication (Box 193, Folder 8)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 60-A
    Notes: Advertisement booklet
  - Item 2: The Shipping Clerk, 1954; Publication (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: The Shipping Clerk, 1955; Publication (Box 193, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol.3:no.2 (1955)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Our unions - Yesterday and today, 1939; Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
    Author: Samuel Shore
    Notes: Speech transcript
  - Item 2: Syrians in the American labor movement, 1939; Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: The Division in the ranks of labor, 1938; Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Welcome to Local 62, Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: What every girl would like and miscellaneous, Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Act before the General Strike is called, Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Don't wait to do it!, Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Modern Union policies, 1939; Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Our Union, 1935; Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 62 (New York, N.Y.)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1-2
  - Item 10: Our Union, 1951; Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.13:no.18
  - Item 11: Our Union, 1952; Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.14:no.6, 11
  - Item 12: Our Union, 1953; Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.15:no.6, 13
  - Item 13: Our Union, 1954; Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.16:no.9
  - Item 14: Our Union, 1955; Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.17:no.8, 10-11
  - Item 15: Our Union, 1956; Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.18:no.1-2, 4
  - Item 16: Our Union, 1957; Publication (Box 193, Folder 9)
    Notes: vol.19:no.3-4, 7, 10
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The fight's just begun: fifty years with Local 66, 1913-1963, Publication (Box 193, Folder 10)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 66 (New York, N.Y.)
  - Item 2: What every member should know, 1946-1955 (Box 193, Folder 10)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 193, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: 40th Anniv. - Local 64 Cloak Buttonhole Makers Union, 1949; Publication (Box 193, Folder 11)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 64 (New York, N.Y.)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 193, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: correspondence, Publication (Box 193, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Our Local 66, 1943; Publication (Box 193, Folder 12)
    Notes: vol.2:no.2-3
  - Item 3: Our Local 66, 1945; Publication (Box 193, Folder 12)
    Notes: vol.4:no.2
  - Item 4: Our Local 66, 1946; Publication (Box 193, Folder 12)
    Notes: vol.5:no.4
  - Item 5: Our Local 66, 1947; Publication (Box 193, Folder 12)
    Notes: vol.6:no.11
  - Item 6: Our Local 66, 1948; Publication (Box 193, Folder 12)
    Notes: vol.7:no.1-12
  - Item 7: Our Local 66, 1949; Publication (Box 193, Folder 12)
    Notes: vol.8:no.1-10
  - Item 8: Our Local 66, 1951; Publication (Box 193, Folder 12)
    Notes: vol.10:no.2-3, 5
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Our Local 66, 1958; Publication (Box 194, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.17:no.4-6
  - Item 2: Our Local 66, 1959; Publication (Box 194, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.18:no.1, 5-9, 11
  - Item 3: Our Local 66, 1966; Publication (Box 194, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.23:no.1-3, 6-13
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Our Local 66, 1955; Publication (Box 194, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.13:no.6
  - Item 2: Our Local 66, 1956; Publication (Box 194, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.14:no.1-3, 5-6
  - Item 3: Our Local 66, 1957; Publication (Box 194, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.15:no.1, 3-7
  - Item 4: Our Local 66, 1958; Publication (Box 194, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.16:no.1-3, 4, 6
  - Item 5: Our Local 66, 1959; Publication (Box 194, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.17:no.2-3